Contact

Dublin, Ireland tupotbhare@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tupotbhare (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Engineering

Research

Computing

Certifications

Tableau Data Analyst/ Specialist Desktop Certification

PL 300 : Microsoft Power BI Data Analyst Associate

Writing Production-Ready ETL Pipelines in Python/Pandas

Agile Fundamentals : Including Scrum and Kanban

Product Analytics Skills Assessment Test

Publications

Blogs on Motivation

Blog on Pursuing one's Hobby in a busy life.

Pursuing Master's - Here's everything you need to know

Tanmay Potbhare

Stamp 1G | M.Sc. Computing (Artificial Intelligence) | Data Analyst | Python | Tableau | PowerBI | SQL | MS Excel | Data Visualization | Machine Learning | Product Analyst

Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland

Summary

Masters in Computing specializing in Artificial Intelligence. Experienced in software development and data analysis. A self-motivated person with organizational skills who has the capability to multitask and be composed under pressure. Good logical thinking and respecting the deadline of any work. Good knowledge in python, data analysis, web scraping, data visualization, and portraying stories through data from working on various college projects.

Skills:

- Python, C, C++
- Data Analysis (Python, SQL, Excel)
- Data Visualization (Power BI, Tableau)
- Web Scraping
- Product Analysis
- Business Analysis
- Agile Methodologies (Scrum, Kanban, Scrumban)

Looking for roles in:

- Data Analyst, Data Engineer, Data Science
- Business Analyst
- Product Analyst
- Software Development

Experience

Brainnest

Data Analyst Trainee November 2022 - Present (1 month)

Bremen, Germany

- Normal Distribution, Z-Score Statistics.
- Performing Reliability Analysis
- ANOVA and Correlation Coefficients

- Using SPSS to manage data, perform analysis, and create visuals
- General Principles used in Data Analytics

Speed TechServe Pvt. Ltd. (OPC) Student Intern May 2017 - June 2017 (2 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

- C / C++ training on an ongoing project.
- HTML training from scratch.

Education

Dublin City University

MSc in Computing, Artificial Intelligence · (September 2021 - August 2022)

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering · (June 2018 - August 2021)

TSSM College of Engineering and Research, Pune, India Diploma, Computer Engineering (June 2015 - May 2018)

Singhad Spring Dale School, Pune, India 10th SSC, Basic Schooling with Specialization in Hindi and German (2004 - 2013)